[music]
[âm nhạc]
Sension
Sension
pe
pe
[music]
[âm nhạc]
lovion
lovion
being wish for loving
being wish for loveing
born
born
worism c
worism c
all like source of wisdom
all like source of wisdom
Non
Non
s
s
[music]
[âm nhạc]
compassion
compassion
welcome with
welcome with
joy white
joy white
buddhism spirit
buddhism spirit
fl the gl
fl the gl
Hai
Hai
[music]
[âm nhạc]
father rescue beast
father rescue beast
joy the
joy the
budism have
budism have
[music]
[âm nhạc]
GL
GL
share and connect
share and connect
love no
love no
more for a peaceful
more for a peaceful
[music]
[âm nhạc]
all living beings
muôn loài chúng
love
sinh yêu quý hòa
peace all
bình muôn Muôn loài chúng
living beings wish to connect with
sinh mong muốn kết nối yêu
love.  Buddhism across the five continents,
thương. Phật giáo khắp năm châu, Phật
Buddhism all over the world, the pagoda shines as a source of
giáo khắp toàn cầu, tháp sáng nguồn trí
wisdom.
tuệ.
Selflessness and compassion joyfully
Vô ngã từ
welcome Buddhism from all five
bi hân hoan đón chào Phật giáo khắp năm
continents.  The wedding procession was magnificent.  Buddhists from all over
châu. Kết xe hoa nhiệm mâu. Phật từ khắp
the world, bound by love and the Eightfold Path,
toàn cầu gắn g tình yêu thương con đường
respectfully celebrate the compassionate Buddha Shakyamuni, the
bát chính đạo kính mừng đức từ phu thích
compassionate Buddha Shakyamuni from the
ca đức từ phù thích
heavenly realm who brings suffering to all beings in this world, whose
ca từ cung trời đau xất đàn sinh cõi ta
flowers bloom, ending hatred and saving people from suffering, and bestowing
bà hoa dài hết oán hận cứu khổ cùng ban
joy.
vui.
Buddhism across the five continents joins hands in
Phật giáo khắp năm châu cũng nắm tay kết
unity, with Buddhists from all over the world united by
đoàn Phật từ khắp toàn câu gắn
love and the Eightfold Path for a
thương con đường bát chính đạo cho thế
world of peace and compassion.
giới hòa bi.
Tí
Tí
congratulates Đức from his
mừng Đức từ
wife
phu thế
[music]
[âm nhạc]
H
H
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
[music]
[âm nhạc]